[
  {
    "no": "01",
    "question": "What does Vue.js?",
    "options": [
      "Build user interfaces",
      "Write server-side code",
      "Manage databases",
      "Create mobile applications"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Build user interfaces"
  },
  {
    "no": "02",
    "question": "What is the primary purpose of Vue.js?",
    "options": [
      "Backend development",
      "Database management",
      "Frontend development",
      "Mobile app development"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Frontend development"
  },
  {
    "no": "03",
    "question": "What does the 'v-bind' directive do in Vue.js?",
    "options": [
      "Binds an attribute to an expression",
      "Defines a variable",
      "Imports a module",
      "Binds a function to an event"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Binds an attribute to an expression"
  },
  {
    "no": "04",
    "question": "Which Vue.js directive is used to handle user input events?",
    "options": ["v-model", "v-bind", "v-if", "v-for"],
    "correctAnswer": "v-model"
  },
  {
    "no": "05",
    "question": "What is a Vue.js component?",
    "options": [
      "A reusable piece of UI",
      "A server-side function",
      "A database schema",
      "An API endpoint"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "A reusable piece of UI"
  },
  {
    "no": "06",
    "question": "What does 'computed' in Vue.js refer to?",
    "options": [
      "Functions that return dynamic data based on other data",
      "Styling rules",
      "Database queries",
      "Routing configurations"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Functions that return dynamic data based on other data"
  },
  {
    "no": "07",
    "question": "What is the purpose of 'v-for' in Vue.js?",
    "options": [
      "To loop through an array",
      "To conditionally render an element",
      "To bind an attribute",
      "To create a new component"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "To loop through an array"
  },
  {
    "no": "08",
    "question": "What is the Vue.js CLI used for?",
    "options": [
      "To create and manage Vue.js projects",
      "To run server-side code",
      "To interact with databases",
      "To handle API requests"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "To create and manage Vue.js projects"
  },
  {
    "no": "09",
    "question": "What does the 'v-if' directive do in Vue.js?",
    "options": [
      "Conditionally renders an element",
      "Binds an attribute to an expression",
      "Imports a module",
      "Defines a variable"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Conditionally renders an element"
  },
  {
    "no": "10",
    "question": "What does Vuex provide in a Vue.js application?",
    "options": [
      "State management",
      "Database access",
      "Routing functionality",
      "Server-side rendering"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "State management"
  }
]
